"use strict";(self.webpackChunkgms_2025_scioly=self.webpackChunkgms_2025_scioly||[]).push([[26],{26:e=>{e.exports=JSON.parse('{"questions":[{"question":"Comparing the microscopy techniques from the previous two questions, what are notable differences between the techniques?","type":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Creates a bright halo","B. Allows live cell viewing","C. Funnels electrons into cells","D. Requires metal coating","E. Allows visualization of small features"],"answer":"E"},{"question":"Select all that apply: which of the following descriptions best describes the bacteria on the right?","type":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Bacillus","B. Cocci","C. Vibrio","D. Staphylococcus","E. Streptococcus"],"answer":["B","D"]},{"question":"What is the purpose of binary fission?","type":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Development of multicellular organisms","B. Endosymbiotic dissolution","C. Lysis of bacterial cells","D. Metabolism of nucleic acids","E. Reproduction into identical daughter cells"],"answer":"E"},{"question":"What is the embedded organelle depicted in the image?","type":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Eyespot","B. Fimbria","C. Flagella","D. Pilus","E. Spirochochete"],"answer":"C"},{"question":"What is the function of this embedded organelle?","type":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Horizontal Gene Transfer","B. Infectivity","C. Transmembrane Nutrient Shuttling","D. Motility","E. Replication"],"answer":"D"},{"question":"Based solely on the bacteria\u2019s preference for low temperatures, what term best describes it?","type":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Acidophile","B. Alkaliphile","C. Halophile","D. Psychrophile","E. Thermophile"],"answer":"D"},{"question":"During a gram stain, gram-positive bacteria stain ___ and gram-negative bacteria stain ___.","type":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Pink; Pink","B. Pink; Purple","C. Purple; Pink","D. Purple; Purple","E. Colorless; Pink"],"answer":"C"},{"question":"A bacteria produces bacteriocin to kill neighboring bacteria to increase the nutrients available for itself. What best describes this relationship?","type":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Competition","B. Commensalism","C. Mutualism","D. Parasitism","E. Predation"],"answer":"A"},{"question":"A rhizosphere bacteria converts ammonia to nitrite. A second rhizosphere bacteria converts nitrite to nitrate. What best describes this relationship?","type":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Competition","B. Commensalism","C. Mutualism","D. Parasitism","E. Predation"],"answer":"B"},{"question":"A Mycobacterium tuberculosis bacterium inhabits and replicates inside macrophage cells. What best describes this relationship?","type":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Competition","B. Commensalism","C. Mutualism","D. Parasitism","E. Predation"],"answer":"D"},{"question":"Which bacterial structure is responsible for antibiotic resistance?","type":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Plasmid","B. Cell Wall","C. Ribosome","D. Flagella"],"answer":"A"},{"question":"Which microbial process is responsible for the fixation of atmospheric nitrogen into a usable form?","type":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Denitrification","B. Nitrification","C. Nitrogen Fixation","D. Nitrogenation"],"answer":"C"},{"question":"Which microbial structure is involved in the attachment of bacteria to surfaces and the formation of biofilms?","type":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Flagellum","B. Pilus","C. Capsule","D. Ribosomes"],"answer":"B"},{"question":"Lytic viruses contribute most to what method of horizontal gene transfer?","type":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Conjugation","B. Transformation","C. Generalized Transduction","D. Specialized Transduction","E. None of the above"],"answer":"C"},{"question":"What is one difference between the life cycle of eukaryotic viruses and bacteriophages?","type":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Bacteriophages inject DNA while eukaryotic viruses inject RNA","B. Bacteriophages enter host cells through fusion","C. Bacteriophages do not have capsomeres","D. Eukaryotic viruses can enter the host cell whole","E. Eukaryotic viruses have helical symmetry"],"answer":"D"},{"question":"Which microscopy technique produced the image on the right?","type":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Bright Field","B. Dark Field","C. Phase Contrast","D. Scanning Electron","E. Transmission Electron"],"answer":"B"},{"question":"Comparing the microscopy techniques from the previous two questions, what are notable differences between the techniques?","type":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Question 1\u2019s technique creates a bright halo surrounding the cell, while Question 2\u2019s technique passes polarized light through a prism, generating two distinct beams of light, which are recombined after passing through cells to create a 3D image","B. Question 1\u2019s technique allows for live cell viewing, while Question 2\u2019s technique requires the cells to be fixed","C. Question 1\u2019s technique funnels electrons into cells to make out organelles, while Question 2\u2019s technique funnels light through the specimens on a dark background","D. Question 1\u2019s technique requires the coating of the cell with an electrical-coating metal like gold, while Question 2\u2019s technique utilizes fluorescent staining","E. Question 1\u2019s allows for live visualization of intracellular organelles while Question 2\u2019s allows for visualization of small features, such as flagella, through contrast"],"answer":"E"},{"question":"Select all that apply: which of the following descriptions best describes the bacteria on the right?","type":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Bacillus","B. Cocci","C. Vibrio","D. Staphylococcus","E. Streptococcus"],"answer":["B","D"]},{"question":"What is the purpose of binary fission?","type":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Development of multicellular organisms from prokaryotes","B. Endosymbiotic dissolution","C. Lysis of bacterial cells into two","D. Metabolism of nucleic acids and proteins","E. Reproduction of bacteria into two identical daughter cells"],"answer":"E"},{"question":"If a bacteria has a dysfunctional DnaA, what step of binary fission (as numbered in the image) would it be paused on?","type":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Step 1","B. Step 2","C. Step 3","D. Step 4","E. Binary fission would still be functional"],"answer":"B"},{"question":"What step of binary fission (as numbered in the image) is the division septum fully formed by the FtsZ complex?","type":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Step 1","B. Step 2","C. Step 3","D. Step 4","E. Binary fission does not form a division septum"],"answer":"D"},{"question":"What step of binary fission (as numbered in the image) does the mitotic spindle separate chromosomes?","type":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Step 1","B. Step 2","C. Step 3","D. Step 4","E. Binary fission does not utilize a mitotic spindle"],"answer":"E"},{"question":"What is the embedded organelle depicted in the image?","type":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Eyespot","B. Fimbria","C. Flagella","D. Pilus","E. Spirochochete"],"answer":"C"},{"question":"What is the function of this embedded organelle?","type":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Horizontal Gene Transfer","B. Infectivity","C. Transmembrane Nutrient Shuttling","D. Motility","E. Replication"],"answer":"D"},{"question":"Select all that apply: what components would not be present in a gram-positive bacteria?","type":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Filament","B. Hook","C. L ring","D. Outer Membrane","E. Peptidoglycan"],"answer":["C","D"]},{"question":"What component in the image would be significantly thicker in gram-positive bacteria?","type":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Cytoplasmic Membrane","B. L ring","C. Outer Membrane","D. Peptidoglycan","E. P ring"],"answer":"D"},{"question":"Based solely on the bacteria\u2019s preference for low temperatures, what term best describes it?","type":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Acidophile","B. Alkaliphile","C. Halophile","D. Psychrophile","E. Thermophile"],"answer":"D"},{"question":"What adaptations would you expect this bacteria to have?","type":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Proteins with less alpha helices","B. Proteins with a larger proportion of beta sheets","C. Higher unsaturated fatty acid chain proportion in membrane for fluidity","D. Higher long fatty acid chain proportion in membrane for rigidity","E. Na+ driven ATP production as opposed to H+"],"answer":"C"},{"question":"During a gram stain, gram-positive bacteria stain ___ and gram-negative bacteria stain ___.","type":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Pink; Pink","B. Pink; Purple","C. Purple; Pink","D. Purple; Purple","E. Colorless; Pink"],"answer":"C"}]}')}}]);